麦琪:那么现在你肯定孩子们都同意大扫除了?
Maggie: So you actually got the kids to agree to do their fair share of
this spring cleaning?
杰森:是的,我只是说这是他们作为家庭成员所应尽的义务,
Jason: I did.I merely pointed out their obligations as members of this family.
他们就马上同意了.
And they were only too happy to pitch in.
开萝尔:本,我们快去吧!
Carol: Ben, Let's go!
迈克:是的,我们还得在那边干很多事呢!
Mike: Yeah, we need, we get a lot of work to do over there.
本:我就来了!嘿!爸爸,谢谢你给我们赚钱的机会.
Ben: I'm coming, I'm coming.Hey, dad thanks for the chance to get rich.
麦琪:你居然贿赂他们!
Maggie: You bribed them.
杰森:没有,我只是说他们可以将房子里的废品清理出去卖给废品收理站,这样我们的房间也就干净了.
Jason: No, I just told them they would clean out of their house the unwanted
junk and they could sell any of them on the garage sale.That way we
get a clean house
麦琪:接着他们就拿到钱了.
Maggie: Then they get to keep all the money.
杰森:他们只拿一半,因为这个是我的提议.
Jason: Half.It was my idea.
本:嘿!这椅子上怎么有个脸?哇,
Ben: Hey, there is a chair with a face on it.
这真是个漂亮的烟灰缸,爸爸怎么会把他扔在这里?
Wow, what's the beautiful ashtray I made to dad doing out here?Dad ol' freak.
爸爸这是个怪人,他很喜欢这个烟灰缸的,他还曾说这是他所收到的最漂亮的礼物!
He loves his ashtray.He said it was the best present he's ever got.
迈克:那是他在说谎.
Mike: He was lying.
本:嘿!难道你觉得烟灰缸有感情吗?
Ben: Hey, don't you think ashtray has feelings too?
迈克:我只是想说这伙计受伤啦!
Mike: I want to say I do, this puppy is in some pain.
本:你得收回你的话.
Ben: You take that back.
迈克:不,
Mike: No.
本:必须收回.
Ben: Yes.
迈克:决不.
Mike: No way.
本:一定要收回.
Ben: Yes way.
开萝尔:我们现在不要再继续这愚蠢的对话,好吗?
Carol: Can we have this stupid conversation later?
迈克:我干吗要继续下去?
Mike: Why would I wanna to do that?
开萝尔:本,把那个放下,
Carol: Ben, put that down and we still have to take out all that junk
我们现在去搬地下室里的东西.
in the basement.
本:对不起,烟灰缸.
Ben: Sorry, ashtray.
烟灰缸:你是有些不对,伙计.
Ashtray: You are sorry.Pal.
本:你好吗?可怜的烟灰缸?
Ben: Hello?Hello?Hardship ashtray?
开萝尔:本,快来!
Carol: Ben, come on!
烟灰缸:这孩子从一堆泥土里把我捏了出来.用了几年后就碎了,
Ashtray: The kid wards me from a simple lump of clay,
接着我们就被丢进了垃圾堆.
breaks Mike and me and Ben a couple of years later on garbage.
运动鞋:然后你就发臭了.
Sneakers: That stinks.
眼镜:不,那是你.
Glasses: No, but you.
迈克:让我猜猜,这是开萝尔的眼镜?
Mike: Let me guess.Carol's glasses?
眼镜:我知道你是迈克的运动些.这可以从空气中闻出来.
Glasses: I knew you are Mike's sneakers.I can feel it in the air.
烟灰缸:是啊,我现在想起了以前在杰森桌上待过的时光,
Ashtray: Well, I think of all those hours I spent on Jason's desk.
还不时地听着他那些疯狂地病人.
Listening to his nutty patients.
运动鞋:我以为你是本的东西.
Sneakers: I thought belonged to Ben.
烟灰缸:我是本送给他爸爸的礼物.
Ashtray: I was a gift from Ben to his dad.
本:妈妈,我想和你谈一分钟.
Ben: You got a minute, mom.
麦琪:当然可以,宝贝.
Maggie: Sure, honey.
本:今年我没有足够的钱买好点的东西.
Ben: I don't have enough money to get dad anything good this year.
麦琪:哦,这周不是给了你双份的零用钱吗?
Maggie: Oh, Didn't you double your allowances this week?
本:是的,但现在四美元没什么好买的,你是不是真的不知道?
Ben: Yeah, but, you can get anything for 4 bucks nowadays.Where you've been?
麦琪:哦,宝贝,礼物值多少钱并不重要.
Maggie: Oh, honey, it's not how much you spent.
本:这应该也让迈克和开萝尔知道.
Ben: Tell that to Mike and Carol.
麦琪:听着,本,
Maggie: Look, Ben, I can't afford to get your father's that Mercedez 450
S as I always wanted, so I am getting him a nice fishing rod
所以我就给他买了个不错的钓鱼竿.他知道我是爱他的,所以他也就会喜欢那鱼竿的.
And he knows I love him, so he'll love it, I hope.Oh, I know.
希望也是如此!我知道你可以用这四美元买些蚯蚓给爸爸当鱼饵.
For 4 dollars, you can get him some worms.
本:妈妈,你不是当真的吧?我是不是还要再送他一个我做的笨拙的烟灰缸?
Ben: Get real, mom?I might as well just give him the stupid ashtray I made?
麦琪:哦,那也很好呀!小鬼,这只要你是用心做的.
Maggie: Oh, that would be fine, punk, as long as it comes from your heart.
本:那烟灰缸倒是挺像我的心.
Ben: It looks like my heart.
麦琪:本,你爸爸并不希望你给他买最好最贵的礼物.
Maggie: Ben, your father is not expecting the biggest expensive gift from you.
本:他不希望?
Ben: He isn't?
麦琪:是的,送什么他都不会介意的.
Maggie: No.Here doesn't care which I get him.
本:太好了.
Ben: Great.
电视:无论是掌权者还是祈求者,有需要的人请跪下.
TV: Power or prayer, be on the need to get down on your knees.
向上帝乞求任何东西,他就会给你的.
And ask God for anything.He shall provide.
本:哦,上帝呀!
Ben: Oh, God!
迈克:你在干吗?
Mike: What are you doing?
本:我刚好在祈求上帝给我些钱.
Ben: I happened to be praying for money.
迈克:本,你不要求钱了.
Mike: Ben, you can't pray for money.Believe me, I've tried.
相信我,我已经试过啦!难道你真的以为上帝会送你支票之类的吗?
Do you actually think God's gonna send you a check or somethin'?
本:阿门!
Ben: Amen!
女士:给穷人些钱?
Lady: Money for the needy?
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thanks.
女士:还给我你这个小强盗.
Lady: Give me that, you little bandit.
把那:但我是穷人呀!
Ben: But I am needy.
女士:我不是施受钱的,我是讨饭要钱的.清醒点!
Lady: I am not giving money away, I am collecting it.Wise up!
迈克:你快走开,我以为你真是灵!
Mike: You out there, I thought you were on to something!
本:但我需要钱.
Ben: But I need money.
迈克:那就加入俱乐部.
Mike: Join the club.
本:但这是给爸爸的钱.
Ben: But this is like for dad.
迈克:这钱是谁的?
Mike: Whose?
本:我的.
Ben: Mine.
迈克:我很忙!
Mike: I am busy.
本:迈克.
Ben: Mike.
迈克:好吧!听着,
Mike: Ok, ok.Alright, Look, Ben, I want you to take this can,
本,我希望你拿着这个罐,装成衣服可怜的样子,
and go from house to house, with that pathetic look,
然后挨家挨户地乞讨过去.我想这样你会赚到钱的.
you could probably make a fortune.
本:谢谢,迈克,还有上帝.
Ben: Thanks, Mike.And thank you, God.
迈克:生日蛋糕!
Mike: The bread for old geezer.
杰森:这没用的,我还这.
Jason: It didn't work, I am still here.
开萝尔:嘿!爸爸,先把好的打开.
Carol: Hi, dad, open the good one first.
迈克:谢谢,开萝尔.
Mike: Thanks, carol.
杰森:嘿!小家伙们.
Jason: Hey, guys.
开萝尔:真是幼稚.
Carol: How juvenile.
迈克:开萝尔,我想说你为什么要让他失望,我是指他已经上年纪了,会受不小打击的.
Mike: Carol, I mean why do you wanna disappoint the man.I mean, he is
aged and can take much of that
杰森:这个先放一下,还是先开开萝尔的吧.
Jason: That settles it.I'll open Carol's first.
开萝尔:不,你不能这样无视这个老人的问题的.
Carol: No, you can be so insensitive about th.e problem of older people.
杰森:本,你送我什么呢?哇!
Jason: Ben, what did you get to me?Wow, Ben, this is fabulous.
本,这真是太棒了.我都不知该说什么好了.
I don't know what to say.
麦琪:我也是,我和这没关系吧?
Maggie: Neither do I.oh, I had nothing to do with this?
杰森:哦,你当然和这没关系.
Jason: Oh, sure you had nothing to do with it.
麦琪:杰森,我没有.
Maggie: Jason, I didn't.
杰森:本?
Jason: Ben?
本:自己想要的东西要靠自己争取,即便是穷人也是一样.
Ben: Deserve things all by itself even if the needy can work out.
杰森:你是从哪里弄到这东西的?
Jason: Where did you get this?
本:这是从隔壁捡到的.每次他家购物超过三百美元后就会扔掉很多东西.
Ben: It from this guy next door.They throw away a lot of cases every
time they spend over 300 dollars
迈克:好了,我想问问你们到底给了他多少零用钱?
Mike: Ok, I've got to ask how many allowances are you giving this kid anyway?
这是:本,这么多钱你是哪里得到的?
Jason: Ben, where did you get the money?
迈克:是呀!这我很感兴趣.
Mike: Yeah, I am interested.
本:好吧,你看,
Ben: Well, see, I needed money.
当时我很需要钱,所以我就挨家挨户地去讨钱.
So I went around all the neighbor houses and I asked for money for the needy.
迈克:哇!
Mike: Whoa.
麦琪:本杰明·西沃,这个主意是谁告诉你的?
Maggie: Benjamin Seaver, where did you ever get the idea like that?
本:上帝和迈克.
Ben: From God, and Mike.
本:这是你的钱,抱歉!慈善组织是我编的.
Ben: Here's your money back.I am sorry, I lied about the charity.
杰森:这没事,儿子,现在我们在家了.
Jason: It's ok, son, we're home now.
本:哦!
Ben: Oh.
杰森:我为你今晚做的事感到骄傲.
Jason: I am proud of what you did tonight.
本:对不起.
Ben: Oops.
杰森:我想你该得到一些教训了.
Jason: Think you learned a lesson.
本:恩.上帝给我主意的时候,我得和你商量一下.
Ben: Uh-huh.When God gives me an idea to check with you first.
杰森:还有吗?
Jason: Anything else?
本:如果你爱某人,你不一定买很好的东西给他.
Ben: If you love somebody, you don't have to spend a lot on them.
杰森:就是这样的,晚安,本.
Jason: That's right.Good night, Ben.
本:爸爸?
Ben: Dad?
杰森:什么?
Jason: Yeah?
本:生日快乐.
Ben: Happy birthday.
杰森:本,这是……
Jason: Ben, It's an...
本:烟灰缸.
Ben: Ashtray.
杰森:我知道了,我刚刚想说的就是这是我收到的最好的生日礼物.
Jason: I know, what I was going to say is it's the best birthday present
I've got from you
烟灰缸:现在没人再要我了,现在没人再要我了.
Ashtray: Now nobody wants me.Now nobody wants me.
开萝尔的眼镜:嘿!我们都有各自的问题.
Carol's glasses: Hey, we all got our problems.
运动鞋:我感觉自己用途蛮大的.
Sneakers: I feel so used.
开萝尔的眼镜:你是的.
Carol's glasses: You are.
运动鞋:但是怎么才能找到知音?
Sneakers: But how can I get soul mates?
迈克:我在对上帝的礼物和历史说早上好.
Mike: I say good morning to God's gift to history.
杰森:看上去你好像在准备一次大的历史考试.
Jason: You look like a guy who is ready for big history tests.
迈克:爸爸,我不是在准备阶段.人名,日期,一切的一切我都记住了.我认为今天我们会被写入历史的,因为今天,1986年2月20日,迈克·西沃度过了难关.
Mike: Daddy, I am just not ready.I've got it all, names, dates, and everything
I think today we'll go down the history as the day Mike Seaver turns the
corner, Feb
杰森:是2月25日.
Jason: It's Feb.25th.
本:嘿!爸爸.
Ben: Hi, Dad.
杰森:嘿!爸爸.
Jason: Hi, Ben
本:这是早餐?
Ben: This is Breakfast?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yes.
本:那么中饭呢?
Ben: What's for lunch?
杰森:那会是个惊喜.
Jason: Surprise.
本:哦,我讨厌惊喜,那里为什么装鞋子?
Ben: A...o, I hate surprises... Why is that fitting in shoes?
迈克:本,那是我的袋子.
Mike: Ben, It's my bag.
本:那里为什么装你的鞋子?
Ben: Why is that fitting in your shoes?
迈克:得了,我要用这个.
Mike: Come on, I need that.
本:甘地,安德鲁·杰克逊,阿尔发贝迪克·孔特豪斯.
Ben: Gandhi, Andrew Jackson, alphabetic courthouse.
迈克:是的,他们都是我的朋友,我背他们的名字不是为了得到好运气.
Mike: Yeah, yeah, they all my buddies.I don't recite them for good luck.
本:你认识一个叫阿尔发贝迪克·孔特豪斯的人?
Ben: You know somebody named alphabetic courthouse,?
迈克:是的,他是黑人,是篮球队的队长.
Mike: Yeah, black guy, captain in the basketball team.
老师:这是多项选择题,考试时间是三十分钟.
Teacher: This is multiple choice.You have 30 minutes.
在你很好完成试卷之前再交给我,现在开始.
Say your papers will be great before your leave.You may begin.
迈克:内战的最后一次战役是:
Mike: The Final round of battle of the civil war was:
A葛底斯堡战役!
A: Battle of Boron.
B盖茨堡战役
B: Battle of Gettysburg.
C星网战役
C: Battle of the Network Stars.
盖茨堡战役!
Gettysburg!
迈克:嘿!我知道这个答案.
Mike: Hey, I actually know this stuff.
老师:在我教学生涯中,也许下面事最震惊的了.这次无线电考试的最高分是迈克·西沃,他考了94分!
Teacher: What's perhaps the biggest shocking in my teaching career since boys studying wire airings
is the highest grade in the class is 94 by Mike Seaver
迈克:我是第一名!
Mike: I am number one!
老师:西沃先生,
Teacher: Mr.Seaver, before we schedule the press conference,
在准备开会前,我得问一下,
I have to ask how does this student whose very name has become synonymous
一个总是得D减的学生是怎么取得这么好的成绩的?
with the phrase D minus, made such grade.
迈克:我该怎么说呢?你得了多少分就是多少分.
Mike: What can I say why I can do it? When you got it, you
got it
老师:哦,现在我知道你是怎么得到高分的啦!
Teacher: Oh, now I see where you got it.
杰森:发生什么啦?
Jason: What happened?
迈克:好吧,考试本身其实没什么好讲的?
Mike: Well, There is nothing to be said about the test itself.
杰森:哦?还是讲讲吧!
Jason: Oh?Say it anyway.
迈克:我通过考试了.
Mike: I passed.
麦琪:完全通过了
Maggie: Completely?
迈克:是!
Mike: Yeah.
杰森:嘿!恭喜你,迈克.
Jason: Hey, congra..., Mike.
麦琪:恭喜.
Maggie: Congratulations.
杰森:我就知道要是课外花点时间是有用的.
Jason: I knew that that little extra study would pay off!
迈克:哦,谢谢.
Mike: Oh, thanks, but I do have some bad news.
但是我还有个坏消息,并且我想你们很难会理解的.
And I think it's difficult to understand.
杰森:你说说是什么?迈克.
Jason: Just say what it is, Mike.
麦琪:你想你还是坐着说吧!
Maggie: I have a feeling you should sit.
迈克:我要告诉你们的肯定会让你们俩都很生气.
Mike: Now what I am about to tell you is going to get both of you
如果你们知道德威特先生是如何对待我的,
quite angry.And you will be outraged at the shoddy treatment I received
你们会很更加愤怒的.但是我不希望你们叫我马上滚开,
from Mr.Dewitt.But I want your words just to go off half cock trying to
从此不再理我或是什么的.
get this guy fired or something.
杰森:我想今晚是不会太太平的.
Jason: I promise to be a fully cock tonight.
迈克:德威特先生指责我作弊.哦,你们冷静一点,我并没有作弊.
Mike: Mr.Dewitt accused me of cheating.Oh, just calm down.I did not cheat.
麦琪:那为什么德威特先生这么说你?
Maggie: Now why would Mr.Dewitt think that?
迈克:你知道吗?甚至我也问了自己为什么?
Mike: You know, I even ask myself that same question after all.
杰森:那好,迈克,你想说什么?
Jason: Well, What would you come up with, Mike?
迈克:我不知道,
Mike: I don't' know.
我猜他是不想看到我考试取得好成绩.
I guess he didn't expect that I did that well on the test.
麦琪:得了,你得好成绩?他得了好成绩,有多少好?
Maggie: Well, you did well?He did well.How well?
迈克:其实我并不在意成绩.
Mike: I rarely pay attention to the grade.
杰森:你得几分?七十?
Jason: Well what did you get?70?
麦琪:七十五?
Maggie: 75?
迈克:不是.
Mike: Well.
麦琪:八十?八十五?
Maggie: 80?85?
迈克:其实.
Mike: Actually.
麦琪:九十?
Maggie: 90?
迈克:加个四.
Mike: 4.
麦琪:九十四?哦,迈克·西沃,我真为你感到羞耻,你怎么能作弊?
Maggie: 94?Oh, Michel Seaver, I am ashamed of you.How could you cheat?
迈克:我没有欺骗.
Mike: I did not cheat.
杰森:你是一百分考了九十四分吗?
Jason: Is this 94 out of a 100?
迈克:我发誓我没有作弊,好了,
Mike: I swear to you I did not cheat.
我以我的荣誉为荣.
Ok, I give you my word of honor.
杰森:好吧,我信你.
Jason: Well, er......I believe you.
迈克和麦琪:真的?
Mike and Maggie: Really?
杰森:好了,我们的儿子既然这样讲了,我们就得信他.
Jason: Well, our son gives us his word.We've gotta believe.
麦琪:你讲得对,我得相信你,迈克.
Maggie: You are right.I believe you Mike.
迈克:哦,
Mike: Oh, thanks.I knew it was so kind of you guys.
谢谢.我知道你们会理解的,
I am sorry for every miserable thing I've ever done that make your world
我为我以前那些令你们难堪的事向你们道歉!
a living hell.
麦琪:我也为怀疑你向你道歉,迈克.
Maggie: And I am sorry I doubted you, Mike.
这件事要是换成你,你也会和我们一样觉得难以置信的.
But It's a tight story to believe if your put yourself in my shoes.
本:妈妈的鞋子比那些蚂蚁堆大多了.
Ben: Mom's shoes are bigger than others' for all the ant heels!
迈克:好了,鞋子.
Mike: All right, the shoes.Thanks, Benny.
谢谢,本.我忘记把最有趣的部分告诉你了.
I forgot to tell you guys as funny as part.
迈克:你们肯定会喜欢的.
Mike: You guys are going to love this.
迈克:你们想知道真相吗?好吧,那我就把真相告诉你们.是的,起先我是打算作弊的,因为我知道那是我通过的唯一方法.因此为了通过这次考试我就把所有的东西都写在鞋上面了.但我也不能完全依靠鞋子呀!我也是有脑子的.不知是怎么回事,但我答题时,我不用看鞋子上的东西,我也知道答案.
Mike: You want to know the truth?Ok, I'll tell you the truth.Yeah, I
was going to cheat.I figured out it's the only way.So I was on
path that I would copy all the stuff onto my shoes cause I had to
pass the test.But somehow I didn't just go on my shoes.I got my
head too.Sure blew me away.But when it came to the time to look
for the answers.I didn't have to.I knew them
麦琪:好吧,迈克,我愿意相信你.
Maggie: Well: I'd like to believe you, mike.
迈克:好的.
Mike: Yeah.
杰森:不过你得承认你还是不知道像亚伯拉罕·林肯这样着名的人是美国的第十七任总统.
Jason: Well, you have to admit you are not exactly the kind o' guy who
has a reputation for knowing things like Abraham Lincoln was the 17th
president?
迈克:是的,他是第十六任.
Mike: Yeah, he was the 16th president.
杰森:对了,格兰特才是第十七任.
Jason: yeah, Grant was the 17th.
迈克:不是的,格兰特是第十八任.
Mike: No, Grant was the 18th.See, uh, Johnson was the 17th.
约翰逊才是第十七任,他是在1865年4月14日林肯遇刺身亡后接任的
He became the president after Lincoln was assassinated on April 14, 1865.
德威特:医生,西沃太太?
Dewitt: Doctor, Ms.Seaver?I am Dewitt.Glad you could come.
我是德威特.很高兴你们能来.我们就直接一点吧!
Why don't we get right down to the business?
杰森:太好了,德威特先生,
Jason: Absolutely, Mike didn't cheat on the examination.Mr.Dewitt.
迈克这次并没有在考试上作弊,这一点我们必须要和你澄清一下.
It's important we clear that up.
麦琪:对他来说,要回答写在写在鞋上的问题,
Maggie: And it would have been so easy for him to do what with all the
那太简单啦!
answers written on the bottom of his shoes.
开萝尔的眼镜:哦,多么感人的故事!我听得心都碎啦!
Carol's glasses: Oh, what a touching story.You broke my heart!
烟灰缸:嘿!
Ashtray: Hey.
开萝尔:本,不会有人愿意出钱买这破台灯的.
Carol : Ben, No one's gonna pay a dime for a broken lamp.
本:所以我才标价5美分.
Ben: That's why mark it 5 cents!
开萝尔:我在想该拿些什么给本.
Carol: I wonder what I could get for Ben.
台灯:运动鞋, 我的老友!难道你这就叫做适应生活吗?
Lamp: So my old friend, the sneakers.This is a fitting into my life.
运动鞋:嘿!我已经说了抱歉.
Sneakers: Hey, I said I was sorry.
台灯:你快闭嘴!
Lamp: Bite your tongue!
运动鞋:嘿!这不是我的错.
Sneakers: Hey, it wasn't my fault.
开萝尔:谁一天在这里乱扔东西?又是谁把这乒乓球鞋放到睡床上的?
Carol: Who is the one who is always straining up around here, eh?Who is
the one going to tie his smelly tennis shoes off the couch
迈克:开萝尔,别忘了还有一个.
Mike: Don't forget the other one, Carol.
开萝尔:哦,在这里!
Carol: Oh, here, catch.
迈克:哦,太好了.
Mike: Oh, Perfect.
开萝尔:还不错,你觉得还能撑起来吗?
Carol: It isn't bad.Do you think it can hold?
迈克:你是在说笑吗?
Mike:Well, are you kidding?
广告上说用这个可以在大峡谷上吊五只大象.
On the commercial this stuff holds five elephants over the Grand Canyon!
本:是啊,广告上讲的不会全是真的吧?
Ben: Yeah, they'll put anything on TV that isn't true?
开萝尔:好吧,现在我们开始清理一下,你俩清理一下垃圾.
Carol: Well, we are going to clear now, you two cleaning up the mess.
迈克:开萝尔,要是把清理好的垃圾到给你,
Mike: Carol, If I clean up the mess for you,
你会发现你自己就刚好是个标准的曲形垃圾箱.
you probably should find yourself a standard trash can up there by the curve!
开萝尔:好了,本,快下来.
Carol: Come on, Ben, get off.
本:我不行,我被粘住了.
Ben: I cannot, I am stuck.
迈克:你在说笑吧?对吧?
Mike: You are kidding, right?
开萝尔:不,不是的.
Carol: No, it isn't .
本:哎呀……
Ben: Au.............
迈克:你尖叫什么?
Mike: What are you screaming about?
本:我不知道,我以前可从没有粘在桌子上过.
Ben: I don't' know, I've never been glued to a table before!
迈克:好了,嗯,把你的手放到我的肩上.然后当我拉你的时候,
Mike: Alright, Hmmm, put your hands around my neck.And when I am pull on you.
用力朝我这边靠,知道吗?一,二,
Throw your weight towards me.Ok?Ready?One, two, three.Oh, no.no... no...
三.不,不!现在该怎么办?
What are we gonna do now?
本:我感觉好多了.
Ben: I feel much better.
开萝尔:你们不想爸妈回家吗?
Carol: You won't want mom and dad to get home.
迈克:到一边去,重要的问题得有好的解决方法.
Mike: Stand side.Big problems go for big solutions.
开萝尔:是什么?
Carol: What is that?
迈克:这是我们这些祈求者的福音!是电子研磨机!
Mike: It's the answer to our prayers!The electric sander!
开萝尔:晚安.
Carol: Good night.
迈克:来吧,你们去哪?
Mike: Come on, where you guys are going?
开萝尔:除了这地方哪都行.
Carol: Anywhere but here.
迈克:伙计们,放轻松点.这是个简单的计划.我们要做的只是在桌子上滑动这东西.明早就可以看见魔术般的变化了.另外我们得找块同样形状的东西.你们觉得如何?
Mike: Oh, guys, relax, relax.Now this is a fool-proof plan.right, all we've
got to do is to glide the sender over the table top couple swoops.We
are standing to perfect magic tries by morning.We have got the maintain the shape
So what do you guys think
开萝尔:本,迈克.
Carol: Ben, Mike.
迈克:伙计们,其实有更简单的办法.我待会告诉爸妈我们把咖啡桌弄坏了.本,开萝尔,你们希望那样做吗?好的,非常棒.别担心,本.某天当我回想起今天的事的时候,你已经是个大人了.你也是,开萝尔.慢慢往上走.
Mike: Guys.It's easier than this.I will tell mom and dad that we ruined
the coffee table.Do you want to do that Ben?Carol?Good, very great.Don't
worry Ben.Some day I look back on this day, you became a man.You
too, Carol.Toddling up
开萝尔:是台灯,是台灯.
Carol: The lamp.The lamp.
迈克:随你吧,如果你有能力买张新桌的话.爸爸和妈妈周六晚上要回来,到时他们第一件要做的事就是随便找一个人问问.
Mike: Ok, If you offer enough for New coffee table.Here mom and dad came
late on Saturdays, so the first thing to mom and dad to go down to
check is the pick-one-up
本:爸爸回来了.
Ben: Dad home, Dad is coming.
迈克:哦,本,坐这别动.
Mike: Oh, Ben, Ben, sit there.Ok, now, just don't move.
迈克,本和开萝尔:嘿!
Mike, Ben and Carol: Hi.
杰森:嘿!各位好!
Jason: Hi, everybody.
麦琪:嘿!小家伙们!
Maggie: Hi, guys.
杰森:晚上好!
Jason: Good evening.
迈克:爸爸,没有什么大不了的事.
Mike: Nothing is great, dad.
麦琪:本?
Maggie: Ben?
本:我也很好
Ben: I'm great too.
麦琪:给你五分钟,马上去睡觉.
Maggie: I want you in bed in 5 minutes.
杰森:迈克,把门锁好,行吗?
Jason: Mike, you lock up, ok?
杰森:小家伙们,明天见.
Jason: See guys in the morning.
迈克,本和开萝尔:再见.
Mike, Ben & Carol: Bye.
麦琪:再见.
Maggie: Bye.
杰森:晚安.
Jason: Good night.
本:哦,不!
Ben: Oh, no.
迈克:你们的晚餐怎么样?
Mike: So what would you guys have for dinner?
迈克:哦,得了,你真以为我是使你留在这里的原因?
Mike: Oh, come on, you really think I am the reason you are all here?
眼镜和台灯:是的.
Glasses and lamp: Yeah.
开萝尔:你们都闭嘴!和你们真是待够了.
Carol: All of you just shut up.It's been enough out here with all of you.
烟灰缸:你觉得比我们好很多?
Ashtray: You think you better than us?
运动鞋:当然,她现在用隐形眼镜.
Sneakers: Of course, she has contacts.
开萝尔的眼镜:自从开萝尔有了隐形眼镜,她把我抛到一边了.
Carol's Glasses: Long after carol got a contact, she cast me.
杰森:哦,开萝尔,你今天过得怎样?
Jason: Oh, Carol, how was your day?
开萝尔:真的,现在一切就很好,
Carol: Everything is fine now, really,
可是不久前还不是这样的.那时我买了新衣服,
I don't know it's not been better lately.
化妆和隐形眼镜,
I mean new clothes, makeup, contact lenses,
只是希望有人能带我去跳舞.但那不是我,
thinking someone to want to take me to a dance, please.
我要变回原来的自己.因为在我努力工作和学习的时候,
It just not me, I mean what I am trying to change.
感觉什么都挺好的.
I was just fine in working hard and in studying.
只要不无聊,不去赶时髦,
I was just fine without trying to be silly and popular.
什么都很好的.我是说我才不稀罕这些冒险啊!
I mean who needs all these risks.Oh, not me.
迈克:我猜今天她过得不好.
Mike: Guess, I mean she didn't have a good day.
开萝尔:妈妈,我想把我的化妆品全扔了.
Carol: Mom.I want to turn on my makeup to the pore.
麦琪:哦,开萝尔,你怎么了?
Maggie: Oh, Carol, what happened?
开萝尔:没什么,没什么!
Carol: Nothing, nothing, I just um,
我只是,叫鲍比一起去正式的舞会,但他拒绝了我.
asked Bobby to the prom and he turned down.
麦琪:哦,宝贝.
Maggie: Oh, honey.
杰森:这太丢脸了.
Jason: It's a shame.
麦琪:亲爱的,这一定有原因吧!
Maggie: Honey, there has to be some reason.
开萝尔:不是我的原因,我想鲍比就根本不想一起去.
Carol: Not me, I mean just he doesn't want to take me.
开萝尔的眼镜:旧球鞋,现在我也像你一样被扔掉了.
Carol's glasses: And now I am tossed out.Like you old shoes.
运动鞋:嘿!
Sneakers: Hey.
开萝尔:这个依据是卡希迪的记录,应该有些用处吧!嘿!我的旧眼镜怎么在这里?
Carol: This is from Cassidy Records, it should be worth something.Hey, what are my old glasses doing out here?
本:你不是再也不用它了吗?所以我……
Ben: Well, you'll never wear it any more?So I .....
开萝尔:你想错了.
Carol: Your thinking is wrong.
本:那我也想留着我的烟灰缸.
Ben: Well, I do want to keep my ashtray.
开萝尔:为什么?
Carol: Why?
本:因为它还是像新的一样.
Ben: It's still as good as new.
开萝尔:的确是的.
Carol: It sure is.
烟灰缸:谢谢,本,谢谢你.
开萝尔:哦,本,这下好了,看来我们是再也不可能把这买出去了.
00:21:39,400
Ashtray: Thank you, Ben, thank you. Carol: Oh, great, Ben.Now we can't even sell it.